http://www.calfund.org/privacy-policy/

HomeTransform LAAbout CCFNonprofitsDonorsAdvisorsDonorConnectNonprofitConnect ContributeLoginDonorConnectNonProfitConnectTransform LAAbout CCFNonprofitsDonorsAdvisors
Privacy PolicyPrivacy and SecuritySince our founding in 1915, the California Community Foundation has been committed to maintaining the confidentiality, integrity and security of personal information entrusted to us by current donors, potential donors, the officers and staff of nonprofit agencies who approach us for funding and the people that they serve.Like all organizations with a Web presence, the California Community Foundation receives standard tracking data: information from your browser, including your IP address and the page you visited, is recorded in our Web site server logs. This data is analyzed internally to determine how to best provide information to visitors to our Web site. No personal information is collected during the tracking process.Online giving transactions are processed on a secure server. We have put into effect appropriate procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Once you provide us with personal or professional information, that data remains confidential. We will not share any information you provide with any individual or organization. We do not knowingly collect or maintain information from those we know are younger than age 13, and no part of our Web site is designed to attract anyone under 13.Links to Other SitesAs a community service, the California Community Foundation provides links to the Web sites for various nonprofits and nonprofit resources. Unless we expressly state otherwise, the California Community Foundation makes no representations whatsoever concerning the content of those sites. A link to a Web site from the California Community Foundation is not an endorsement, authorization, sponsorship or affiliation with respect to such site, its owners or providers. When leaving www.calfund.org, we recommend you check the privacy policy of the site you are visiting before providing personal information.Copyright StatementCopyright in the text materials contained in this Web site is owned by the California Community Foundation. These text materials may be used, downloaded, reproduced or reprinted, provided that this copyright notice appears on all copies and provided that such use, download, reproduction or reprint is for noncommercial or personal use only. The text materials contained in the Web site may not be modified in any way.Copyright in the photographs, illustrations, artworks and other graphic materials are reserved to the California Community Foundation and/or the copyright owners (licensors). Prior permission to use, download, reproduce or reprint any photograph, illustration, artwork or other graphic material must be obtained by the copyright owner, regardless of intended use.Any use of “California Community Foundation,” its logo, or text or graphic materials contained in this Web site in any manner to express or imply endorsement, sponsorship, affiliation or association of the user with or by the California Community Foundation, is strictly prohibited.Disclaimers of Warranties & LiabilityBecause of the number of possible sources of information available through this Web site, and the inherent hazards and uncertainties of electronic distribution, there may be delays, omissions and inaccuracies in such information. The California Community Foundation cannot and does not warrant the accuracy, completeness, correctness, noninfringement or fitness for a particular purpose of the information available through this Web site, nor do we guarantee that this Web site will be error-free and continuously available.Web Links to This SiteYou may establish a hypertext link to this site from your Web site, so long as the page containing the link properly attributes the linked site to the California Community Foundation and does not state or imply any sponsorship of your site by the California Community Foundation. We may revoke this permission at any time. Without prior written consent of the California Community Foundation, you may not create a link to this site that incorporates or relies upon, in whole or in part, any content from any page on this Web site, or that incorporates any copyrighted or otherwise intellectual property of the California Community Foundation.Changes to Privacy PolicyThe California Community Foundation may amend this privacy policy from time to time. Such changes will be publicly posted in this area of our Web site.Questions or Suggestions: If you have any questions or suggestions, please send an e-mail to the webmaster.Last revised: 10/8/15what matters is not how we differ, but what we shareshare CCF          221 S FIGUEROA ST #400LOS ANGELES, CA 90012  MapPHONE: 213-413-4130FAX: 213-383-2046EMAIL: info [@] calfund [.] orgMAKE A DONATIONOPEN A FUNDReserve Meeting SpaceDonorConnect LoginNonProfitConnect LoginNewsroomCareersAccessibility StatementTerms Of UsePrivacy Policy Transform LAAbout CCFNonprofitsDonorsAdvisors        © 2020 California Community Foundation. All Rights Reserved.
